{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbolt_and_Lightfoot",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "resource/Robert_Daley_(producer)",
    "human_readable": "The producer of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Robert Daley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9410383701324463,
            "question": "What was the role of Robert Daley in Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8243087530136108,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who produced Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8240839242935181,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8106411695480347,
            "question": "Robert Daley is the producer for which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7942388653755188,
            "question": "Name a film produced by Robert Daley."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6567255258560181,
            "question": "Who directed Thunderbolt and Lightfoot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6092339754104614,
            "question": "Is Robert Daley known for producing movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5110651254653931,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other films produced by Robert Daley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49867919087409973,
            "question": "What type of work does Robert Daley do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41826871037483215,
            "question": "When was Thunderbolt and Lightfoot released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Robert Daley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3172_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of work does Robert Daley do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3172_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about any other films produced by Robert Daley?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3172_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robert Daley known for producing movies?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3172_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3172_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The query is whether the information in the documents supports the triple \"The producer of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Robert Daley\".\n\nUpon reviewing the documents, we can see that:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3172/re-ranker-msmarco/88.txt mentions \"producer = Robert Daley\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3172/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt also mentions \"Producer: Robert Daley\"\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple.\n\nThe final answer is:\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Robert Daley was a producer for the film \"Thunderbolt and Lightfoot.\" Therefore, the statement \"The producer of Thunderbolt and Lightfoot is Robert Daley\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}